**?** JSlusark

jslusark.github.io/portfolio

✓ slusark.jessica@gmail.com

**J** +4917636301966

Parlin, Kreuzberg

in linkedin.com/in/jessicaslusark

# **EDUCATION**

# **Career Foundry**

🚃 Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

Berlin, Germany
 FullStack Web Development
 Bootcamp

#### **She Codes**

a Aug 2022 & Dec 2022

Berlin, Germany
Intro to Web Development

## Scuola Internazionale di Comics

**==** 2010 - 2013

Naples, Italy
Digital art, illustration and
animation for games and comics

## "L' Orientale" University of Naples

**2009 - 2011** 

Naples, Italy
 Literature and Linguistics of
 Asia and America

# **SKILLS**

## Front-End:

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JavaScript, React.js / Create-React-App (CRA), React Native, Angular, Angular Material, jQuery, React Bootstrap

#### **Back-End:**

Node.js, Express, RESTful API, Firebase

## **Testing & Debugging:**

JestCucumber, Puppeteer.

## Tools:

Expo, Google Lighthouse, Recharts, Atatus, Parcel, Postman, Git, Github

#### **Databases:**

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Mongoose, SQL

#### Languages:

Native - English, Italian Fluent - Spanish Basic - French, German

# **Jessica Slusark**

# **PROFILE**

Full-Stack Web Developer with previous tech sales experience within the mobile industry (advertising, saas, analytics, marketing, app testing, publishing). In my previous roles, working closely with developers significantly increased my interest in web development. This hands-on experience deepened my understanding of user needs, data intricacies, and product dynamics. Having built my web development foundation with courses such as SheCodes (part-time) and CareerFoundry (full-time), I continue to build upon the training I was provided with. Collaboration and consistent growth drives my work, fueling my dedication to learning and adapting.

# **∂PROJECTS**

Pokedex App

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

**8** MyMovieList API

JavaScript, MongoDB, Express, Node.js, Postman, PostgreSQL, Mongoose **My Movie List (React)** 

React, Node.js, Express, Parcel, React Bootstrap

**8** My Movie List (Angular)

Angular, Node.js, Angular Material **6** Chat App

React, React Native, Expo, Google Firebase **8** Meet App

React / Create-React-App, CSS, JestCucumber, Puppeteer, Atatus, Lighthouse, Recharts

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **SensorTower** - Enterprise Account Executive, Gaming (EMEA)

Berlin, Sep 2021 - Jan 2023

Engaged with mobile game developers at SensorTower, offering tailored marketing analytics solutions. Translated intricate datasets into actionable insights, aiding developers in navigating the mobile gaming trends.

## PlaytestCloud - Account Executive and Manager

Berlin, Jul 2020 - Sep 2021

Served as a bridge between game studios and playtesting tools at PlaytestCloud. Communicated technical product changes, ensuring understanding and alignment among app/game developers and UX designers.

# TheLazyRed.com - Freelancer

Berlin, Jan 2019 - Jun 2020

After relocating to Berlin and inspired by its vibrant entrepreneurial scene, I decided to use my sales background and passion for art, to offer custom game art services tailored to mobile game developers.

## **Unity -** Business Development Manager

London, Nov 2015 - Dec 2018

Partnered with game developers at Unity, introducing advertising solutions and indie game strategies. Presented interactive design mockups, advocating for optimal in-game ad experiences and impact on game performance.

## Game Analytics - Mobile publishing assistant

London, Feb 2015 - Nov 2015

Collaborated with game developers at Game Analytics. Transformed analytics into comprehensible insights and actively participated in game development discussions, honing gameplay and UI.